It's gone.
What does it look like?
Okay. Shall we?
Ready?
Guy Guy Chance
So this time
Pool Day
Pool Day in Okinawa
We solicited instagrams from all of you
What we want to ask girls girls
What is the end of summer like?
Pick up the questions, how would you like to answer them?
Girls Girls Up
what do you think?
Yes, so
I'm loosening up
Today, I'm going to be loose.
Let's all have fun answering these questions
Okay, first of all, I want to ask you girls-girls.
They're cute.
I think I'll start with my daughter.
I know exactly how you feel.
Confidence is important.
Confidence is the most important thing.
The member who learns to dance the fastest...
Let's say, KID?
KID?KID?
They're all fast.
where are you coming from?
Uh, but, uh, okay.
Hold on a sec.
just in case
eh?
Mobo.
Hey, Mobo.
I'm coming.
Mobo-chan.
I'm so mad with you, Mobo-chan.
I've been talking about you.
I thought maybe you'd be the one to remember.
Oh, my God.
I'll always remember you.
You're so thin.
I'd like to know the MBTI for member zoom.
enfp infj
I'm a good match for Kura, aren't I?
That's great.
Introverts and extroverts...
I'd like to know if that's true.
Maybe it will change.
This is how I feel now.
Thank you for all your questions.
Thank you very much.
It's your favorite.Your favorites.
Maximizer at night
After all, it's nice to go to Rikan on a rainy day.
You have a nice voice.
I've got something for you today.
This is what I'm wearing today.
I'm using pink.
I'm using yesterday's lip color.
I think it's No. 2. I brought No. 2 for the lip team.
You've grown up, Ninami.
Thank you, but I'm not sure what part of me has matured.
Compared to the past.
I've been going out more with my friends, to places that are farther away.
Like a trip. -Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I see a lot of things, even trivial things.
What is your favorite dressing?
Dressing.
I thought that was the dressing for the clothes.
That's cool.
Which one do you usually use?
Cabbage detergent from a pork cutlet restaurant.
Carrot-based, maybe.
Carrot and onion... a little bit.
I'm a green perilla.
I've always wanted to try it, but I can't seem to pass it up. What do I do then?
Depends.
But I'm listening.
Do you regret doing it or not doing it? Which would you choose? Do you want to have regrets for doing something or regrets for not doing something? Which would you choose?
Regret for doing it.
That's what I mean.
It's great just to have the desire to try something in the first place.
And if you can put it into action, you'll have even more confidence.
Let's keep going forward with what we want to try!
Fighting!
I'm rooting for you!
After all...
Do you want to live alone?
I don't think so.
What?
No?
Not really.
Well, except for Ikurei, but... he lives at home.
I'm done with that.
I've already put distance between us.
Yeah.
You want to do it, Kina?
I'd like to... soon.
I'd like to do it soon.
Is there someone you want to see the most?
Yes, I do.
Who is it?
Yes, sir.
Is there? You asked me.
Yes, I'm here. I'm here.
You're all here.
Yes, sir.
When you recruited me, you asked me who I was. He asked me.
I'm asking you.
What perfume do you recommend?
I don't use it much.
But I use it a lot.
I like shampoo
White Savon.
I like it.
Savon.
Hair mist or something like that.
Jo Malone.
I don't know if I'm allowed to read this, but...
It's good, right?
I can't do this kind of thing with this kind of thing.
What type of man do you like?
Well, he's my type.
Let's take them one by one.
But you know what I've said before.
Let's do it together.
Like this.
It's also an ideal. It's what I'm most proud of.
That's hard. That's hard.
You said it so well.Well, you've said it yourself.
He said that a man of integrity is the best.
A man of decency. That's important, I know.
I'm a sensible person, too. Can I say the same thing? Can I say the same thing?
Shiitake mushrooms, shiitake mushrooms, shiitake mushrooms, shiitake mushrooms...
I think it's good. I like it.
Tell me something cute about Claire that only the members know.
What's cute about Claire-chan?
The way she suddenly gets all flustered.
She's cute? She's cute. She's cute.
She's cute. -She's cute.
She's cute.
Yeah, she just got kicked... at the foot of the pool.
He just kicked me. That's so scary.
It's scary. -Isn't it scary?
Actually, it's a little scary. I can't see.
I can't see. - Scary.
Next end, from Al-Al.
Thank you so much.
I don't know what I'm going to wear now.
This is cool.
I think this is cute.
Please wear the Sucia collaboration trophy hoodie.
Please put it on.
That's so cute!
It's so cute!
We'll have this on the floor at the end of the summer.
When the 24-hour TV show is over. When 24 hours TV is over
I feel the end of summer.
I can hear the sound of autumn insects
I hear heartbreak songs.
Yeah, especially.
Oh, no. Eat me.
Hooks, they're singing about heartbreak.
You and me at the end of the summer.
Oh, I see.
I'm gonna eat all the leftover sawmilling I have left at home.
That's true. What's that feeling?
I want to eat the house
I want to eat the house I want to eat the house
It's convenient.
I want to eat the house.
It's easy to be together.
Well, summer vacation...
It's fun, isn't it?
Mysterious fever
You're right. Summer breeze...
That's how I feel.
When you do cartoons, too.
That's true.
It's a little different.
There's a lot of this, too.
I miss shorts.
I'm going to be a girl, you know?
It's gonna get a little chilly.It's gonna get a little cold.
I'll still wear it in the winter.
But you can say I'm fashionable and patient.
And you never finish your assignments.
I know what you mean.
The sun sets early.
I know.
It's already dark.
But it's true, you can feel how fast the sun is setting.
Season
Oh, it's summer, it's so late.
That's true.
Everyone seems to be lonely.
I'm going to miss you.
Summer is fun and I'll miss you.
I'll miss you.
I know what you mean.
I'm lonely because I'm lonely
I'm going to miss you.
The point is, it's almost like a room, but I'll give you this recommendation.
It's like an ends shop, but with better quality.
That's what I'm talking about.
I've been looking at this a lot.
That's why.
That's good.
It's thick.
MundinMundin
You know what?
Uh.
thick
This
Alive.
Yes, it is.
Right.
That's what I'm talking about. Hime-chan and the countdown, and all that.
It would be nice to see the countdown in a big place someday.
I'm not going home for New Year's.
I know.
I wonder how long I'll be gone.
Someone stepped on my foot.
Who's that?
You stepped on my foot.
He overdoes it.
He's going too far.
What are you stepping on my foot for?
I didn't say anything.
I'm just saying it's a bad idea.
You're right.
Thank you very much.
It's not every day I get a chance to do something like this.
It's so rough.
It's funny.
I thought you were supposed to be having fun with your work.I thought we were supposed to enjoy the work first.
I guess so.
What's with the thumbnail?
It's bad.
I think I want to stuff it with thumbnails.
What's that video?
Hey, over here.
Well, well, well.
Thank you very much.
If you liked this video, please click the Good button and subscribe to our channel!
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Oh, scary.
Oh, my gosh.
Scary.
This is it. I'm going.
That's it. I'm going.
Is that it?
Yeah. - Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God! Beautiful!
Beautiful!
Nice ball!
Oh, my gosh!
Beautiful!
Beautiful!Beautiful!
In the meantime, let's try to do our best to make it wide open.
I can do anything.
Beautiful!
I'm scared.
I know.
It's a challenge!
The challenge.
This.
This one.
You said we don't have much time.
What do you mean?
It won't fall off?
It's not good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, guys.
Here we go.
Challenge, challenge, challenge!
Challenge! Challenge! Challenge!